

847-528-2326 adamkosecki@gmail.com

full resume at: adamkosecki.com

I am Adam Kosecki, a highly-analytical product developer with 10+ years of experience. I create things that are clean; from beautiful, straightforward, comprehensible design elements to robust & readable code.

I strive to understand a problem from all angles before outlining a solution. My solutions are a fair compromise between form and function, fanciness and efficiency, seriousness and fun.

I am a leader. I make decisions when appropriate, and defer or delegate without shame. People respect me and enjoy working with me.

#### **TECH & TOOLS**

JS, Ember.JS, Cordova, Bootstrap, MySQL, Sphinx Full-Text Search, PHP, Phalcon, AWS, Photoshop. Illustrator AWS

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, Programming Emphasis Minor in Psychology

Western Illinois University 2000-2004

### HISTORY

# **SpotMii**

CO-FOUNDER / CTO / DEVELOPER
2017 - PRESENT

SpotMii was created to provide fitness consumers a way to discover new and exciting fitness facilities, and streamline the payment and check-in process for individuals that frequent multiple gyms. Users purchase single-use passes for drop-in access and scheduled classes. Payments and scheduling are handled in-app.

As a co-founder and CTO of SpotMii, I successfully designed, built, and deployed demonstrative beta versions of our apps that enabled us to secure an angel round of funding. I completed and launched the app in early 2019.

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Geo-located, on-demand, two-sided marketplace
- Single codebase SPA/JS/Cordova app deployed to iOS App Store and Google Play
- Three apps built and deployed: Consumer facing app, affiliate app for gym owners, and an intranet for internal moderation.
- · Ember.js SPA design & implementation
- PHP/Phalcon API design & implementation
- MySQL DBA
- · AWS infrastructure

## MogulMind

CO-FOUNDER / CTO / DEVELOPER 2016 - 2018 I designed and built MogulMind: an Ember.js SPA that provides insight into real estate investments, helping users to increase ROI and make better investment decisions.

MogulMind is a first-to-market web app providing traditional RE investment calculations for the modern world, as well as proprietary investment advice through AI.

As the founder's first partner, I took MogulMind from napkin idea to launch and customer acquisition. I was the root of anything technical or design related.

- · SPA: Ember.js design & implementation
- · REST API: PHP/Phalcon/MySQL design & implementation
- · Marketing website design & implementation
- · AWS infrastructure